[
	{
		"response_c": "Site 32",
		"response_b": "Site 20",
		"correct_answer": "d",
		"question": "In which Site is SCP-682 contained?",
		"response_a": "Site 12",
		"response_d": "None of them"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "End of Humanity",
		"response_b": "Destruction of reality",
		"correct_answer": "a",
		"question": "What does an XK Class Scenario mean?",
		"response_a": "End of the world",
		"response_d": "End of Civilization"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "An abnormal former French president",
		"response_b": "A statue with a Mexican hat",
		"correct_answer": "d",
		"question": "What is SCP 420-J",
		"response_a": "An alien fish",
		"response_d": "A huge weed"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "The administrator of the site where they operate",
		"response_b": "The representatives of council 05",
		"correct_answer": "a",
		"question": "Who does the ethics committee obey ?",
		"response_a": "To the Council O5",
		"response_d": "The Supervisor"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "Containment of anomalies",
		"response_b": "Management of abnormal terrorist attacks",
		"correct_answer": "c",
		"question": "What is the main mission of FIM Lambda-5",
		"response_a": "Abnormal zone exploration",
		"response_d": "Field agent training"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "During an Automated Response Initiative type RA-1",
		"response_b": "During a BLACK code",
		"correct_answer": "a",
		"question": "Under what circumstances should the FIM Lambda-5 be called ?",
		"response_a": "During a MAGENTA code",
		"response_d": "When Class-D members rebel"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "To save the Class-D staff",
		"response_b": "To protect foundation members",
		"correct_answer": "d",
		"question": "Why does the ethics committee exist?",
		"response_a": "They have no use, they're useless",
		"response_d": "To set limits for the foundation"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "The Thau-5",
		"response_b": "The Omega-1",
		"correct_answer": "c",
		"question": "If a staff revolt breaks out, which Fim should intervene ?",
		"response_a": "The Alpha-1",
		"response_d": "The Omicron Rhô"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "A breeding circus clown",
		"response_b": "SCP-2094",
		"correct_answer": "a",
		"question": "Who is Bobble the Clown?",
		"response_a": "A clown visible only to children",
		"response_d": "SCP-2912-3"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "Study and understand them before confining them",
		"response_b": "Contain them and attempt to destroy them",
		"correct_answer": "a",
		"question": "What is the Foundation's standard procedure for containing SCP ?",
		"response_a": "Contain them in a containment cell in accordance with their dangerousness and specific needs",
		"response_d": "Make them appear in the light"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "A living mechanical scarecrow",
		"response_b": "Robert Bumaro",
		"correct_answer": "b",
		"question": "Who is the most important figure in the 'Church of the Broken God' interest group?",
		"response_a": "SCP-914",
		"response_d": "SCP-2217"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "Performing a sacrifice in the name of the Scarlet King",
		"response_b": "Telling SCP-231-7 a story",
		"correct_answer": "d",
		"question": "What is the 110-Montauk procedure?",
		"response_a": "An extremely violent procedure that consists of ████████ SCP-231-7",
		"response_d": "Nobody knows"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "Cool",
		"response_b": "Good",
		"correct_answer": "c",
		"question": "Are we ... yet ?",
		"response_a": "Not Cool",
		"response_d": "Thaumiel"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "Yellow",
		"response_b": "Green",
		"correct_answer": "a",
		"question": "Five years, ten months, twenty-eight days",
		"response_a": "Red",
		"response_d": "Violet"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "●●|●●●●●|●●|●",
		"response_b": "Him",
		"correct_answer": "c",
		"question": "The one whose name must not be spoken",
		"response_a": "SCP-2521",
		"response_d": "●●|●●●●●●●"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "A mixture of esoteric practices of the main monotheistic religions",
		"response_b": "Is an emergency protocol in a class PK scenario",
		"correct_answer": "d",
		"question": "Procedure 220-Calabasas ...",
		"response_a": "Prevents the deconfinement of SCP-106",
		"response_d": "Is useless"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "KLEPPSTAD",
		"response_b": "SCP-3008-2",
		"correct_answer": "b",
		"question": "The store is now closed, please exit the building",
		"response_a": "SCP-2030",
		"response_d": "SKUBB"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "SCP-002",
		"response_b": "SCP-3008",
		"correct_answer": "c",
		"question": "I produce charming, all-natural causy furniture, Who am i ?",
		"response_a": "A furniture store",
		"response_d": "SCP-1025"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "It's square",
		"response_b": "SCP-055",
		"correct_answer": "b",
		"question": "This is not round",
		"response_a": "SCP-5000",
		"response_d": "SCP-002"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "He's dead",
		"response_b": "He's alive",
		"correct_answer": "d",
		"question": "What is ████████ ?",
		"response_a": "●●|●●●●●|●●|●",
		"response_d": "████████"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "Class D",
		"response_b": "Class W",
		"correct_answer": "b",
		"question": "What's the only class of agent that can remind you of something ?",
		"response_a": "Class A",
		"response_d": "Class G"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "The Clipper",
		"response_b": "The Sculptor",
		"correct_answer": "a",
		"question": "That you are. One Hawaiian, one meat lovers, is that right, gentlemen ?",
		"response_a": "Ruiz Duchamp",
		"response_d": "The Man"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "Herman Fuller",
		"response_b": "Dr. Clef",
		"correct_answer": "c",
		"question": "He has the biggest abnormal circus in the world, it is ... ?",
		"response_a": "Dr Bright",
		"response_d": "The Snipper"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "Class G",
		"response_b": "Class D",
		"correct_answer": "d",
		"question": "Which agent class can be used to enter a state of temporary amnesia ?",
		"response_a": "Class C",
		"response_d": "Class I"
	},
	{
		"response_c": "wowwee u kild ursefl",
		"response_b": "Is this how rationality tries to exist? Perhaps we should think more carefully about this in a more serene environment, don't you think ?",
		"correct_answer": "a",
		"question": "KILL YOURSELF! WOWWEE! GO KILL YOURSELF! WOWWEE! Wowwee…",
		"response_a": "Nobody dies",
		"response_d": "15:18:20"
	}
]